

Angelo Cordon
Web Designer & Developer

◀ San Francisco, California, US

(925) 487-6562

angelocordon@gmail.com

angelocordon.com

in 🗘 🛩 Bē 🛞

BACKGROUND

ABOUT

San Francisco-based web designer and developer. I love building products that push for intuitive user experiences. I've designed and built websites and web applications for Vikario, The Great Baby Romp, Sovereign Gaming League, Shiploop and many others.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Co-Founder, Lead Developer, A Vivid Visual

Jan, 2015 - Aug, 2015 **②** 7 months

Co-founder and lead developer for boutique design and development firm. A Vivid Visual caters to entrepreneurs and businesses in need of pushing their brand and products to the next level, while keeping up to date with modern web and design standards.

- o Client relations, directed project branding, lead developer.
- Clients include Shiploop, Life Well Organized, Sovereign Gaming League, The Great Baby Romp
- Develop web-based MVPs using Ruby on Rails, Heroku and AWS

Graphic Design Lead, The UPS Store

Mar, 2010 - Jan, 2015 **②** 4 years 10 months

Worked with local small businesses on designing graphical assets from postcards, menus, to posters and banners.

- Established a graphic design department within a franchised retail store to compliment and push printing revenues.
- o Clients included Roostertail, La Creme Spa, Crown and Crumpet, Japantown Cherry Blossom Festival

Co-Founder, RocketShip

Jan, 2009 - Jan, 2011 **②** 2 years

RocketShip aimed to make shipping for consumers 10x easier by aggregating prices from UPS, FedEx and USPS in one window. Skip the long lines at postal locations by printing the shipping labels right from home.

- Branded and designed the web application.
- Created various marketing materials.
- o Designed and developed landing pages with a combination of PHP and LESS.
- Used Google Analytics to A/B test landing pages.

</> SKILLS

Web Development

HTML Sass/LESS jQuery Ruby on Rails PHP Jekyll Twitter Bootstrap Susy

Visual Design

Web Design UI/UX Photoshop Illustrator Branding and Identity Design

EDUCATION